French Painting Photograph Collection
Yale University Arts Library
French Painting Photograph Collection
1900-2005
VRC 20
Yale University Arts Library
90.4
217 boxes
Collection of medium format mounted black and white and color reproductions of French painting. Content varies from original photographic prints to reproductions from magazines and other published sources. Some sections have accompanying clippings folders.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Collection of medium format mounted black and white and color reproductions of French painting. Content varies from original photographic prints to reproductions from magazines and other published sources. Some sections have accompanying clippings folders.
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by artist. Individual artist material is further subdivided by location of the work. The individual artist portion is preceded by a grouping arranged chronologically and then by location.
Painting, French; Photographs; Reproductions
- General --Artists Unknown (Box 1)
  - 13th – 20th centuries (2 photographs) (Box 1)
- Romanesque (566 photographs) (Box 1)
  - 12th century Romanesque (28 photographs) (Box 1)
  - Areines (22 photographs) (Box 1)
  - Berzy-La-Ville (4 photographs) (Box 1)
  - Brinay (Cher) (54 photographs) (Box 2)
  - Coudes (Loir Cher) (5 photographs) (Box 2)
  - Eure Loire, Notre Dame (21 photographs) (Box 3)
  - Lavardin (23 photographs) (Box 3)
  - Le Liget (29 photographs) (Box 4)
  - Le Mangy (Indre) (3 photographs) (Box 4)
  - Les Roches (5 photographs) (Box 4)
  - Loches (Indre & Loire) (3 photographs) (Box 4)
  - Meobecq (3 photographs) (Box 4)
  - Montmorillon (10 photographs) (Box 4)
  - Poitiers (Box 5)
    - Bapistery of S. Jean (11 photographs) (Box 5)
    - Notre Dame La Grande (5 photographs) (Box 5)
  - Poce, Loir Cher (6 photographs) (Box 5)
  - S. Aignan Sur Cher (44 photographs) (Box 5)
  - S. Gilles de Montoire (37 photographs) (Box 6)
  - S. Jacques de Guerets (40 photographs) (Box 7)
  - S. Loup (6 photographs) (Box 7)
  - S. Savin (Vienne) (107 photographs) (Box 8)
    - S. Savin I (60 Photographs) (Box 8)
    - S. Savin II (48 photographs) (Box 9)
  - Souday (3 photographs) (Box 10)
  - Tavant (31 photographs) (Box 10)
  - Vicq (66 photographs) (Box 11)
- Gothic (Box 12)
  - 13th century (1 photograph) (Box 12)
    General
    Includes a folder of miscellaneous clippings
  - 14th century (Box 12)
    - Drawings (26 photographs) (Box 12)
    - Paintings (Box 12)
      - Wilton Diptych (22 photographs) (Box 12)
- 15th century (Box 13)
  - Drawings (6 photographs) (Box 13)
  - Paintings (59 photographs) (Box 13)
    - School of Amiens (11 photographs) (Box 14)
    - School of Avignon (16 photographs) (Box 14)
      - Avignon Pieta (8 photographs) (Box 14)
    - School of Burgandy (8 photographs) (Box 14)
    - Masters (3 photographs) (Box 14)
      - Master of Aix (15 photographs) (Box 14)
      - Maitre de Moulins (15 photographs) (Box 15)
        - Autun (5 photographs) (Box 15)
        - Moulins (8 photographs) (Box 15)
        - Paris (7 photographs) (Box 15)
      - Master of S. Giles (17 photographs) (Box 15)
- 16th century (Box 16)
  - Drawings (6 photographs) (Box 16)
  - Paintings (30 photographs) (Box 16)
    - Paris (23 photographs) (Box 16)
    - School of Fontainebleau (30 photographs) (Box 17)
- 17th century (Box 17)
  - Drawings (3 photographs) (Box 17)
  - Paintings (19 photographs) (Box 18)
- 18th century (Box 18)
  - Drawings (16 photographs) (Box 18)
  - Paintings (22 photographs) (Box 18)
- 19th – 20th century (18 photographs) (Box 18)
  - Individual artists (Box 18)
  - A, miscellaneous (16 photographs) (Box 18)
    Includes two folders of miscellaneous clippings
    - Aligny, Claude-Felix de, 1798-1871 (14 photographs) (Box 19)
    - Andre, Albert, 1869-1954 (8 photographs) (Box 19)
    - Angrand, Charles, 1887-1926 (17 photographs) (Box 19)
    - Anquetin, Louis, 1861-1932 (7 photographs) (Box 19)
    - Arp, Hans, 1887-1966 (27 photographs) (Box 19)
    - Aubry, Emily, 1880- (5 photographs) (Box 20)
    - Aved, Jacques-Andre, 1702-1766 (4 photographs) (Box 20)
    - Aved, Jacques-Andre, 1702-1766. 4 photographs (Box 20)
  - B, miscellaneous (Box 20)
    - Ba-Be (24 photographs) (Box 20)
    - Bi-Bouli (25 photographs) (Box 20)
    - Boulo-Bun (16 photographs) (Box 20)
    - Bail, Joseph, 1862-1921 (3 photographs) (Box 21)
    - Balthus (Balthasar Klossowski), 1903- (23 photographs) (Box 21)
    - Barye, Antoine-Louis, 1795-1895 (8 photographs) (Box 21)
    - Basachet, Marcel, 1862- (4 photographs) (Box 21)
    - Bastien-Lepage, Jules, 1848-1884 (27 photographs) (Box 21)
    - Bauchant, Andre, 1873- (4 photographs) (Box 21)
    - Baudry, Paul-Jacques, 1828-1886 (9 photographs) (Box 22)
    - Baugin, Lubin, 1610-1663 (7 photographs) (Box 22)
    - Bazaine, Jean, 1904- (6 photographs) (Box 22)
    - Bazille, Frederic, 1841-1870 (26 photographs) (Box 22)
    - Bellegambe, Jean, 1480-1535 (9 photographs) (Box 22)
    - Berard, Christian, 1902- (5 photographs) (Box 22)
    - Beraud, Jean, 1849-1936 (17 photographs) (Box 23)
    - Bernard, Emile, 1868-1941 (25 photographs) (Box 23)
    - Bertin, Jean Victor, 1775-1842 (17 photographs) (Box 23)
    - Besnard, Paul Albert, 1849- (19 photographs) (Box 23)
    - Biard, Francois Auguste, 1800-1881 (5 photographs) (Box 24)
    - Bidauld, Jean-Joseph-Xavier, 1758-1846 (10 photographs) (Box 24)
    - Blanche, Jacques Emile, 1861-1942 (10 photographs) (Box 24)
    - Boilly, Louis Leopold, 1761-1845 (Box 24)
      - Drawings (7 photographs) (Box 24)
      - Paintings (41 photographs) (Box 24)
    - Bombois, Camille, 1883- (5 photographs) (Box 24)
    - Bonheur, Rosa, 1822-1899 (21 photographs) (Box 25)
    - Bonnard, Pierre, 1867-1947 (6 photographs) (Box 25)
      - Paintings (109 photographs) (Box 25)
      - Paintings II (Box 26)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (27 photographs) (Box 26)
        - Leningrad (6 photographs) (Box 27)
        - New Haven (3 photographs) (Box 27)
        - New York (14 photographs) (Box 27)
        - Paris (19 photographs) (Box 27)
        - Washington (27 photographs) (Box 27)
    - Bonnat, Leon, 1833-1922 (13 photographs) (Box 28)
    - Bonvin, Francois, 1817-1887 (15 photographs) (Box 28)
    - Boucher, Francois, 1703-1770 (Box 28)
      - Drawings (37 photographs) (Box 28)
        - Paris (9 photographs) (Box 29)
        - Stockholm (10 photographs) (Box 29)
        - Vienna (8 photographs) (Box 29)
      - Paintings (34 photographs) (Box 29)
        - Miscellaneous (38 photographs) (Box 30)
          - London (33 photographs) (Box 30)
          - New York (14 photographs) (Box 31)
          - Paris (38 photographs) (Box 31)
          - Stockholm (5 photographs) (Box 31)
          - (Washington 9 photographs) (Box 31)
    - Boudin, Eugene, 1824-1898 (24 photographs) (Box 32)
      - Private Collection (6 photographs) (Box 32)
        - Paul Mellon Collection (25 photographs) (Box 32)
        - Museum Collection (27 photographs) (Box 32)
        - Glasgow (4 photographs) (Box 33)
        - New York (6 photographs) (Box 33)
        - Paris (6 photographs) (Box 33)
        - Washington (12 photographs) (Box 33)
    - Bouguereau, William Adolphe, 1825-1905 (61 photographs) (Box 33)
    - Bourdon, Sebastien, 1616-1671 (16 photographs) (Box 34)
      - Paris (8 photographs) (Box 34)
    - Boutet de Monuel, Bernard, Sr., 1850-1913 (2 photographs) (Box 34)
    - Boutet de Monuel, Bernard, Jr., 1884- (14 photographs) (Box 34)
    - Braque, Georges, 1882-1963 (Box 35)
      - Date unknown (45 photographs) (Box 35)
      - -1909 (31 photographs) (Box 35)
      - 1910's (38 photographs) (Box 36)
      - 1920's (28 photographs) (Box 36)
      - 1930's (35 photographs) (Box 37)
      - 1940's (23 photographs) (Box 37)
    - Brascassat, Jacques Raymond, 1804-1867 (13 photographs) (Box 37)
    - Brenton, Jules adolfe, 1827-1906 (27 photographs) (Box 38)
    - Broederlam, Melchior, c.1388 (14 photographs) (Box 38)
  - C: Miscellaneous. (58 photographs) (Box 38–39)
    - Cabanal, Alexandra, 1824-1889 (16 photographs) (Box 39)
    - Caillebotte, Gustave, 1848-1894 (33 photographs) (Box 39)
    - Callot, Jacques, 1592-1635 (14 photographs) (Box 39)
    - Canella, J.(4 photographs) (Box 40)
    - Caron, Antoine, 1515-1593 (6 photographs) (Box 40)
    - Carolus-Duran, Charles-Emile, 1838-1917 (6 photographs) (Box 40)
    - Carpeaux, Jean Baptiste, 1827-1875 (14 photographs) (Box 40)
    - Carriere, Eugene, 1849-1906 (37 photographs) (Box 40)
    - Cazin, Jean Charles, 1841-1901 (2 photographs) (Box 40)
    - Cezanne, Paul, 1839-1906 (2 photographs) (Box 41)
      - Drawings (23 photographs) (Box 41)
      - Paintings (137 photographs) (Box 41–42)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 43)
          - A-K (36 photographs) (Box 43)
          - L-Z (28 photographs) (Box 44)
        - Chicago (10 photographs) (Box 44)
        - London (20 photographs) (Box 44)
        - Moscow (4 photographs) (Box 44)
        - New Haven (6 photographs) (Box 44)
        - New York (16 photographs) (Box 45)
          - Metropolitan Museum of Art (16 photographs) (Box 45)
          - Museum of Modern Art (6 photographs) (Box 45)
        - Paris (13 photographs) (Box 45)
          - Louvre (24 photographs) (Box 45)
        - Philadelphia (9 photographs) (Box 46)
        - Washington (21 photographs) (Box 46)
        - Zurich (5 photographs) (Box 46)
    - Chabas, Paul, 1869- (12 photographs) (Box 46)
    - Champaigne, Phillipe de, 1602-1674 (48 photographs) (Box 47)
    - Chardin, Jean Baptiste (Box 48)
      - Drawing (6 photographs) (Box 48)
      - Paintings (10 paintings) (Box 48)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (38 photographs) (Box 48)
        - London (10 photographs) (Box 48)
        - New York (10 photographs) (Box 48)
        - Paris (48 photographs) (Box 49)
        - Washington (21 photographs) (Box 49)
    - Charonton, Enguerrand, ac.1410-1466 (8 photographs) (Box 50)
    - Chasseriau, Theodore, 1819-1856 (38 photographs) (Box 50)
    - Chintreuil, Antoine, 1816-1873 (26 photographs) (Box 50)
    - Claude Gellee (Lorrain), 1600-1682 (Box 51)
      - Drawings (19 photographs) (Box 51)
        - Harlem (9 photographs) (Box 51)
        - London (31 photographs) (Box 51)
        - New York (6 photographs) (Box 51)
        - Paris (10 photographs) (Box 52)
      - Paintings (23 photographs) (Box 52)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 52)
          - A-L (34 photographs) (Box 52)
          - M-Z (21 photographs) (Box 53)
        - London (17 photographs) (Box 53)
        - Madrid (9 photographs) (Box 53)
        - Paris (16 photographs) (Box 53)
    - Claus, Emil, 1849-1924 (3 photographs) (Box 54)
    - Clouet, Francois, 1505-1572 (Box 54)
      - Drawings (16 photographs) (Box 54)
      - Paintings (47 photographs) (Box 54)
    - Clouet, Jean, 1485-1540 (Box 55)
      - Drawings (8 photographs) (Box 55)
      - Paintings (17 photographs) (Box 55)
    - Clouet, School of (12 photographs) (Box 55)
    - Constant, Benjamin, 1845-1902 (3 photographs) (Box 55)
    - Cormon, Fernand, 1895-1924 (Box 55)
    - Corneille de Lyon, 1534-1574 (24 photographs) (Box 55)
    - Corot, Jean Baptiste Camille, 1796-1875 (Box 56)
      - Drawings (14 photographs) (Box 56)
      - Paintings (92 photographs) (Box 56)
        - Private Collection (30 photographs) (Box 57)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 58)
          - A-G (44 photographs) (Box 58)
          - H-O (41 photographs) (Box 58)
          - P-Z (24 photographs) (Box 59)
        - Boston (8 photographs) (Box 59)
        - Chicago (10 photographs) (Box 59)
        - Cleveland (6 photographs) (Box 59)
        - Edinburgh (6 photographs) (Box 59)
        - London (15 photographs) (Box 59)
        - New York (21 photographs) (Box 60)
        - Paris (10 photographs) (Box 60)
          - Louvre (79 photographs) (Box 60)
        - Philadelphia (16 photographs) (Box 61)
        - St. Petersburg (8 photographs) (Box 61)
        - Washington (44 photographs) (Box 61)
    - Cottet, Charles, 1863-1925 (18 photographs) (Box 62)
    - Courbet, Gustave, 1819-1877 (24 photographs) (Box 62)
      - Private Collection (9 photographs) (Box 62)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 62)
        - A-C (22 photographs) (Box 62)
        - D-N (35 photographs) (Box 63)
        - O-Z (13 photographs) (Box 63)
      - Boston (7 photographs) (Box 63)
      - Budapest (5 photographs) (Box 63)
      - London (25 photographs) (Box 63)
      - New York (Box 64)
      - Northampton (4 photographs) (Box 64)
      - Paris (3 photographs) (Box 64)
        - Louvre (23 photographs) (Box 64)
        - Petit Palais (16 photographs) (Box 64)
      - Philadelphia (10 photographs) (Box 65)
      - Washington (11 photographs) (Box 65)
    - Curtois, Jacques, 1621-1675 (6 photographs) (Box 65)
    - Courture, Thomas, 1815-1879 (10 photograph) (Box 65)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 65)
        - A-K (22 photographs) (Box 65)
        - L-Z (21 photographs) (Box 65)
      - Boston (11 photographs) (Box 66)
      - London (6 photographs) (Box 66)
    - Coypel, Charles Antoine, 1694-1732 (10 photographs) (Box 66)
    - Coypel, Noel Nicolas, 1628-1707 (6 photographs) (Box 66)
    - Cross, Henri Edmond, 1856-1910 (30 photograpphs) (Box 66)
  - D (Box 67)
    - Da-Dr (25 photographs) (Box 67)
    - Ds-Dz (27 photographs) (Box 67)
    - Dagnan-Bouveret, Pascal Adolphe J., 1852-1929 (8 photographs) (Box 67)
    - Danloux, Henri-Pierre, 1753-1809 (8 photographs) (Box 67)
    - Daubigny, Charles Francois, 1817-1878 (1 photographs) (Box 67)
      - Drawings (3 photographs) (Box 67)
      - Paintings (13 photographs) (Box 68)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 68)
          - A-M (47 photographs) (Box 68)
          - N-Z (17 photographs) (Box 68)
        - Cincinnati (9 photographs) (Box 69)
        - London (9 photographs) (Box 69)
        - Paris (15 photographs) (Box 69)
        - Washington (5 photographs) (Box 69)
    - Daumier, Honore, 1808-1879 (Box 69)
      - Drawings (54 photographs) (Box 69)
      - Drawings II (Box 70)
        - New York (9 photographs) (Box 70)
        - Paris (14 photographs) (Box 70)
      - Paintings (45 photographs) (Box 71)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 71)
          - A-K (17 photographs) (Box 71)
          - L-Z (17 photographs) (Box 72)
        - Baltimore (6 photographs) (Box 72)
        - Glasgow (12 photographs) (Box 72)
        - New York (14 photographs) (Box 72)
        - Paris (30 photographs) (Box 73)
        - Washington (12 photographs) (Box 73)
        - Winterthur (9 photographs) (Box 73)
        - Questionable Attributed (20 photographs) (Box 73)
    - David, Jacques-Louis, 1748-1825 (Box 74)
      - Drawings (28 photographs) (Box 74)
      - Paintings (11 photographs) (Box 74)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 74)
          - A-M (31 photographs) (Box 74)
          - N-Z (14 photographs) (Box 75)
        - New York (9 photographs) (Box 75)
        - Paris (56 photographs) (Box 75)
        - Washington (8 photographs) (Box 76)
    - Decamps, Gabriel Alexandre, 1803-1860 (21 photographs) (Box 76)
      - Boston (6 photographs) (Box 76)
      - Chantilly (10 photographs) (Box 76)
      - London (12 photographs) (Box 76)
      - Minneapolis (5 photographs) (Box 76)
      - Paris (12 photographs) (Box 76)
    - Degas, Edgar, 1834-1917 (1 photograph) (Box 77)
      Includes three folders of miscellaneous clippings
      - Drawings (19 photographs) (Box 77)
        - Private Collection. (19 photographs) (Box 77)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (18 photographs) (Box 77)
        - New York (11 photographs) (Box 77)
        - Paris (9 photographs) (Box 78)
        - Williamstown (25 photographs) (Box 78)
      - Paintings (Box 78)
        - Location Unknown ( 80 photographs) (Box 78)
        - Private Collection (59 photographs) (Box 79)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 79)
          - A-L (30 photographs) (Box 79)
          - M-Z (45 photographs) (Box 80)
        - Boston 12 photographs) (Box 80)
        - Cambridge (6 photographs) (Box 80)
        - Chicago (10 photographs) (Box 80)
        - Edinburgh (8 photographs) (Box 80)
        - Glasgow (6 photographs) (Box 81)
        - London (20 photographs) (Box 81)
        - New Haven (7 photographs) (Box 81)
        - New York (14 photographs) (Box 81)
          - Metropolitan Museum of Art. (32 photographs) (Box 81)
        - Paris (54 photographs) (Box 82)
        - Washington (25 photographs) (Box 82)
    - Delacroix, Eugene, 1798-1863 (Box 83)
      - Drawings (13 photographs) (Box 83)
        - Private Collection (25 photographs) (Box 83)
        - C.R. Marx Collection (9 photographs) (Box 83)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (11 photographs) (Box 83)
        - Paris (22 photographs) (Box 84)
        - Williamstown (11 photographs) (Box 84)
      - Paintings (29 photographs) (Box 84)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 85)
          - A-K (41 photographs) (Box 85)
          - L-Z (32 photographs) (Box 85)
        - Boston (7 photographs) (Box 85)
        - London (15 photographs) (Box 86)
        - New York (9 photographs) (Box 86)
        - Paris (15 photographs) (Box 86)
          - Louvre (57 photographs) (Box 86)
        - Washington (10 photographs) (Box 87)
    - Dellaroche, Paul, 1797-1856 (18 phototgraphs) (Box 87)
    - Delaunay, Robert, 1865-1941 (27 photographs) (Box 87)
    - DeMarne, Jean Lois, 1744-1829 (16 photographs) (Box 87)
    - Denis, Maurice, 1870-1943 (32 photographs) (Box 88)
    - Derain, Andre, 1880-1954 (2 photographs) (Box 88)
      - Drawings (3 photographs) (Box 88)
      - Paintings (Box 88)
        - Date Unknown (74 photographs) (Box 88)
          - Paintings Date Unknown I (Box 88)
          - Paintings Date Unknown II (Box 89)
          - -1909 (43 photographs) (Box 89)
          - 1910's (7 photographs) (Box 90)
          - 1920's (28 photographs) (Box 90)
          - Munich (6 photographs) (Box 90)
    - Desboutin, Marcellin-Gilbert, 1823-1902. (7 photographs) (Box 90)
    - Desnoyer, Francois, 1894- (4 photographs) (Box 90)
    - Desportes, Alexander-Francois, 1661-1743 (9 photographs) (Box 90)
    - Detaille, Jean-Baptiste Edouard, 1848-1912 (18 photographs) (Box 91)
    - Devambez, Andre-Victor, 1867- (3 photographs) (Box 91)
    - Deveria, Achile, 1800-1857 (6 photographs) (Box 91)
    - Deveria, Eugene Francois, 1805-1865 (7 photographs) (Box 91)
    - Diaz de la Pena, Narcisse V., 1807-1876 (19 photographs) (Box 91)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 91)
        - A-K (23 photographs) (Box 91)
        - L-Z (28 photographs) (Box 92)
      - The Hague (7 photographs) (Box 92)
      - Leningrad (8 photographs) (Box 92)
      - London (7 photographs) (Box 92)
      - Minneapolis (5 photographs) (Box 92)
      - Paris (9 photographs) (Box 92)
    - Dinet, Etienne, 1861-1922 (3 photographs) (Box 92)
    - Dore, Gustave, 1832-1883 (12 photographs) (Box 92)
    - Drouais, Francois, 1727-1775 (18 photographs) (Box 93)
      - New York (7 photographs) (Box 93)
      - Paris (6 photographs) (Box 93)
    - Dubois-Pillet, Albert, 1845-1890 (14 photographs) (Box 93)
    - Dubuffet, Jean, 1901- (57 photographs) (Box 93)
      - Dubuffet I (Box 93)
      - Dubuffet II (Box 94)
    - Duchamp, Marcel, 1887-1968 (6 photographs) (Box 94)
      - New Haven (11 photographs) (Box 94)
      - Philadelphia (36 photographs) (Box 94)
    - Dufresne, Charles, 1876-1936 (15 photographs) (Box 94)
    - Dufy, Raoul, 1877-1953 (49 photographs) (Box 95)
      - Private Collection (9 photographs) (Box 95)
        - DeBeers Consolidate Mines Ltd. (7 photographs) (Box 95)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (11 photographs) (Box 96)
      - New York (13 photographs) (Box 96)
      - Paris (10 photographs) (Box 96)
    - Dughet, Gaspard, 1615-1675 (21 photographs) (Box 96)
    - Dumonstier, Daniel, 1574-1646 (7 photographs) (Box 96)
    - Dumonstier, Etienne & Pierre (7 photographs) (Box 96)
    - Duplessi-Bertaux, Jean, 1747-1819 (4 photographs) (Box 96)
    - Duplessis, Joseph, 1725-1802 (9 photographs) (Box 97)
    - Dupre, Jules, 1811-1889 (7 photographs) (Box 97)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 97)
        - A-K (19 photographs) (Box 97)
        - L-Z (20 photographs) (Box 97)
      - The Hague (7 photographs) (Box 97)
      - Paris (18 photographs) (Box 97)
    - Dutilleux, Henri-Joseph, 1807-1865(10 photographs) (Box 98)
  - E (5 photographs) (Box 98)
    - Etcheverry, Denis (3 photographs) (Box 98)
  - F (Box 98)
    - Fa-Fla (8 photographs) (Box 98)
    - Fle-Fr (13 photographs) (Box 98)
    - Fantin-Latour, Henri (21 photographs) (Box 98)
      - Private Collection (8 photographs) (Box 98)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 99)
        - A-E (21 photographs) (Box 99)
        - F-Z (21 photographs) (Box 99)
      - London (7 photographs) (Box 99)
      - Paris (8 photographs) (Box 99)
      - Washington (14 photographs) (Box 99)
    - Fautrier, Jean, 1898-1964 (5 photographs) (Box 100)
    - Filiger, Charles, 1863-1928 (10 photographs) (Box 100)
    - Filliard, E. (7 photographs) (Box 100)
    - Flandrin, Hippolyte, 1809-1864 (9 photographs) (Box 100)
    - Flandrin, Paul Jean, 1811-1902 (10 photographs) (Box 100)
    - Fleury, Francois, 1804-1858 (10 photographs) (Box 100)
    - Forain, Jean-Louis (Box 100)
      - Drawings (17 photographs) (Box 100)
      - Paintings (19 photographs) (Box 100)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (9 photographs) (Box 100)
    - Foujita, Tsuguharo, 1886-1968 (9 photographs) (Box 101)
    - Fouquet, Jean (Box 101)
      - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 101)
        - A-M (12 photographs) (Box 101)
        - N-Z (14 photographs) (Box 101)
    - Fragonard, Jean-Honore, 1732-1806 (Box 101)
      - Drawings (29 photographs) (Box 101)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 102)
          - A-O (12 photographs) (Box 102)
          - P-Z (13 photographs) (Box 102)
        - Besancon (10 photographs) (Box 102)
        - Paris (10 photographs) (Box 102)
      - Paintings (22 photographs) (Box 102)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 103)
          - A-Le (12 photographs) (Box 103)
          - Li-Z (14 photographs) (Box 103)
        - London (10 photographs) (Box 103)
        - New York (25 photographs) (Box 103)
        - Paris (11 photographs) (Box 104)
          - Louvre (32 photographs) (Box 104)
        - Washington (16 photographs) (Box 104)
    - Francais, Francois Louis, 1814-1897 (14 photographs) (Box 104)
    - Fresnaye, Roger de la, 1885-1925 (19 photographs) (Box 105)
    - Friesz, Othon, 1879-1949 912 photographs) (Box 105)
    - Froment, Nicolas, 1470-1876 (14 photographs) (Box 105)
    - Fromentin, Eugene, 1820-1876 (27 photographs) (Box 105)
  - G (Box 106)
    - Ga-Ge (21 photographs) (Box 106)
    - Gi-Go (13 photographs) (Box 106)
    - Gr-Gu (19 photographs) (Box 106)
    - Gauguin, Paul, 1848-1903 (Box 106)
      - Mappe (Box 106)
      - Miscellaneous Private Collection (Box 107)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 108)
          - A-B (27 photographs) (Box 108)
          - C-M (33 photographs) (Box 108)
          - N-Z (19 photographs) (Box 108)
        - Boston (7 photographs) (Box 109)
        - Chicago (18 photographs) (Box 109)
        - Edinburgh (7 photographs) (Box 109)
        - Essen (10 photographs) (Box 109)
        - Leningrad (17 photographs) (Box 109)
        - London 11 photographs) (Box 109)
        - New York (17 photographs) (Box 109)
        - Paris (28 photographs) (Box 110)
        - Washington (15 photographs) (Box 110)
    - Gavarni, Paul, 1804-1866 (5 photographs) (Box 110)
    - Gerard, Francois (7 photographs) (Box 110)
      - Paris (14 photographs) (Box 110)
      - Versailles (10 phototgraphs) (Box 110)
    - Gericault, Theodore, 1791-1824 (Box 111)
      - Drawings (41 photographs) (Box 111)
      - Paintings (22 photographs) (Box 111)
        - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 111)